Happy New Year everyone!
Four years of video?
Oh!
I'm not used to saying that.
Today, the weather is a bit dicey.
But today, the four of us have started the year 2024.
I'd like to go to the first Modell!
Yay! I'm so happy!
We can all go to our first Modell together. It's our first time, so we might as well be happy.
I'm also looking forward to taking it while walking
It's so hard to get a good look at the road!
Everyone take a little picture of yourselves!
Today, you know, with this view.
I'm sure some of you are already aware of this.
I'll tell you which shrine we're going to today.
I'd like to go to Enoshima Shrine.
Yay! I'm so happy!
I've always wanted to go there.
I'm so happy.
What do you think? Have you guys been to Enoshima?
Yeah, I have.
No, we haven't.
First time?
It's about 10 steps to the shore.
Oh! I'm so excited. Oh! I'm looking forward to it.
That's nice.
I've been there.
I'm in Kanagawa, so I often go there.
I'm in Kanagawa, too.
I'd like to introduce you today.
Leave it to Kanagawa Prefecture
Leave it to me. I haven't been there recently for a long time.
Leave it to me.
It was raining a little bit earlier today.
Yeah.
I thought the weather was going to be a little bad today.
Miraculously, it stopped.
You're a sunny girl, aren't you?
I'm a sunny girl.
VS love of the eyes today!
Let's have fun, all of us!
I'm off.
Okay.
I'm walking on foot.
Yes, sir!
This is not the first curve.
Here we are. We're here.
Shall we go?
Let's go around.
And, and, and, and, and...
Here we are.
There it goes!
We've arrived at the Bronze Torii!
Wow!
Amazing!
At last, from here!
If you go up from here...
That's it, isn't it?
Enoshima Shrine.
It's about to open.
I'm looking forward to it!
By the way, this Enoshima Shrine
Enoshima Shrine is dedicated to three sister goddesses.
Do you know who they are?
Three sisters?
You mean three, right?
Yes, there are three.
Healthy, right?
Choji, healthy?
Good, good, good. We also have facemanship.
Study-related. Then, the correct answer is...
He was originally associated with the sea and water. Originally, it was a god related to the sea and water.
but it also has the meaning of improving the arts.
It's a word that means "performing arts".
Perfect? That's perfect.
There's also Myouon Benzaiten, the god of music and the arts.
He's the god of music and the arts.
He's perfect for us.
Today, I want you to do the right thing.
And tell him how grateful we are for what he did for us last year.
From now on...
We've got a lot of debuts coming up, so let's all go to the shrine together and make a lot of wishes.
I'm looking forward to warming up in the snow today... walking... a little more gradual slope...
I'm looking forward to it!
Oh, wow!
There's even a doctor fish!
Doctor fish?
And then there's this challenge where you get to try to resist the sensation.
They're 100 yen for a bunch of them.
Wow!
It's starting to look like Mt.
Here we are! Here we are!
That's great!
Oh, there are stairs!
The stairs are amazing!
This way... it's turning.
Oh, my God. That's great.
Yay!
Samnee.
I'm buying it, Samnee.
So we've arrived at Enoshima Shrine, so let's all climb up!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
The Enoshima Shrine
I love stairs in shrines.
I know.
They're so nice.
Aren't they different from regular stairs?
Yes, they are.
I usually take the stairs at the train station.
They make me gasp.
Yeah, they are.
Dragons are cool.
Year of the role?
You're old enough to play?
Yeah, I think so.
Oh, no.
Oh, I mean, isn't it just this year?
Oh, it says so.
Oh, wait, I'm in my second year.
I'm in my second year.
2004. 2004
latter half of a year
Yeah. - Yeah?
What? Rear?
Later.
It's a bad time.
I'm in my senior year.
I'm in my senior year next year.
I'm in my second year.
Rear Yr.
You were born in '16? Ayumi?
No, I was born in '15.
I was born in '15.
But I'm already 20.
That's why I was born early.
So I'm not old at all?
Yeah.
Oh, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle!
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle
Oh, finally.
The sound.
I knew it!
It's so true.
It's called a role-playing magazine.
It's floating. You're floating.
I can feel it.
You're floating.
You're floating
That's great!
We're here.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors, rock, scissors!
That's great!
What's going on?
Can I take a picture of this?
Can you see it? Are they all here?
There's one of them.
Men are here.
I'm here.
We're here.
We made it!
I'm so happy.
It's amazing!
The air is so clear.
So clear.
It's so clear.
It's because we came up here.
It's so peaceful.
It's red.
It's red. Red
Benzaiten
Eh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, that's the one
Yes, yes, yes
Benzaiten-sama
God of the arts and musicians
So many!
Let's go!
Let's go to the temple
Let's go.
Here they come.
Thank you.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
We have to go to the "Solemie" now, too.
That's true.
We haven't even started the tour yet.
We haven't even reached the finals yet.
I'll make sure the tour is a success.
Yeah, that's good.
When do we do this?
Seino
Yes, ma'am.
Is it done? Is it over?
It's over. It's over.
Excuse me.
Please take care of him.
Please.
Be sure.
You talk really fast when you join in.
Is that so?
I keep hearing the refrain over and over again.
Like, "Thank you for everything.
You talk really fast.
He said it very fast.
We should be thankful for last year.
I want to draw an ema (votive picture tablet) with everyone.
Wanna draw an ema?
Hell, yeah.
There are many kinds of pictures.
What would you like?
It has a sense of being at a convenient point.
I agree.
Let's make it an ema (votive tablet).
I'll buy this for the first year.
Let's draw the future of Niyazhioe.
Thank you very much.
I got an ema.
Yay! Yay.
That's great. I did it right.
I made it into a picture of performing arts and music.
Yes, you did.
Can I write it down?
Yes, you can. Go ahead.
I'll leave it to Momoko.
JOY's debut and tour.
Your handwriting's beautiful.
Yes, Momoko's handwriting is beautiful.
Clap for Momoko.
Success.
That's great.
I'll write it again.
May you be loved by many people for a long time.
Thank you.
Can I make it bigger?
Sure.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad.
You put a lot of thought into it, don't you?
It's very thoughtful.
Thank you. Thank you.
It's nice.
It's nice. That's good. - That's good.
Great... Wishes for everyone who could write.
I'm so happy.
Ta-da! I wrote it!
I think this will make our tour and debut a success!
Oh! I made it!
May Nearly Call Joy's debut and first tour be a success!
May they be loved by many people!
Yay!
That's so easy to understand.
Okay, then, everyone, now that we've all successfully drawn a picture man, let's draw a fortune.
I don't know if you know this, but there's a kind of fortune called "mizu-mikuji".
I don't know if you know this, but there's this thing called a mizu mikuji.
I wanted to do that.
I wanted to do that!
I think we should do it together.
It's huge!
I'm so happy! Is it just plain paper? It's like it floats when you put it on.
Isn't it amazing?
It's my first one of this type.
My first time!
Isn't this it? There's a water fortune.
Is this it?
This one?
It's like a ray of light.
I wonder what it feels like.How does it feel?
Oh, my God!
It's true! It doesn't say anything.
Is there such a thing as great luck?
We should definitely wake up to that.
All I know is "daikichi".
I'd like to try the mizu mikuji with everyone right away!
Yay!
It's all curled up!
I've never seen this type before!
It says "mizu-mikuji" on it.
It's nice.
Good?
What shall we do?
This one.
This one!
It's got a number on it.
Here!
Here.
Do they all have numbers on them? Down there.
It's written right there.
Thirty.
All together.
All together?
Are you kidding me?
Thirty and 19. 30 and 19
30?
Is it Aomoriya then?
Are they the same?
The "30" means there's a scent.
Together?
What?
Wow!
This is it?
Okay, I'll go check it out.
I'm in.
I'm gonna be nervous when I get this.
Here it comes!
That was fast!
No, no, no!
I'm with you!
That was fast.
It's coming out.
Oh, my God!
Are we together?
I'm with you.
That's great.
We're the same.
Is this for real, too?
Here we go. number of nights
Today's
Today
It's true!
Oh, shit.
It's like this.
There's so many of them, and they're all together like this.
What?
And it's work.
Oh, no.
They'll know we're rehearsing.
Me and...
Lennon was lucky.
We're the same.
I'm so surprised.
But I'm glad you got a medium.
It's not bad, right?
It's good, isn't it?
So, with Rijelka...
How was your home?
I didn't write anything. I didn't write it.
Just now.
You sure about that?
I'll see you at home.
You're lucky you're not using it.
Health is the only thing.
The strength of the mind is the life force.
It's what really kills diseases.
Keep a strong heart.
This is for money.
Ethical income is good luck when you spend it.
Spend it, it's good luck.
Not Lennon.
Lennon spent too much.
Let's save it.
I'm excited.
Are we going to tie the knot?
I'll tie all the knots except for the big one.
I'll tie it then.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Great luck.
Yay!
Everyone's perfect.
I tied it.
It's big luck. Great luck.
From now on.
It's up to you.
Good luck to all of you.
I'd like to write it down.
Here it is
Greedy beauty talisman
Beauty.
Beauty
I can pursue beauty
It seems that there is a good luck charm
I wish we could all write
I'm so happy
I'll become a beauty
It's called the Greedy Beauty Charm.
Greedy?
Greedy.
We're going on tour, too.
People will take pictures of us, right?
With the amulet.
Take it.
Take it with you.
I want to be beautiful.
Here.
I love it!
Smile. Smile
I have many faces.
Beautiful skin
Beautiful hair.
That kind of thing
I'm going to make you smile.
That's why we all
I bought a good-luck charm
Everyone has their own
the beauty you want
We each got a beauty talisman we wanted.
What about Momochan?
Beautiful amulet
Beautiful shape is nice!
And you, Yuukapyun?
I got the skin charm.
Nice.
It was red.
Red makeup.
Purple.
I want my skin to look like that.
That's right.
I'm Bisho.
I'm going to be the one with the charming smile
Yellow
I made it a beauty I made a beauty.
Hey, it's Sara.
That's nice.
Let's take this on tour with us.
Let's put it somewhere.
I'm glad we're all here.
Here you go.
I'm gonna polish it up.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
So today we all
We all had our first mordel at Enoshima Shrine today.
How was it?
It was so much fun!
We can all go together.
It's not often that we get to go on a private trip together.
That's why I was so happy.
We're still on tour.
We still have the finals to go.
We still have a lot of time left on the tour.
I hope we can finish the tour.
We are waiting for her debut,
I want to give Nia more and more power and momentum,
We're all going to do our best.
We will do our best. I will do my best.
Best wishes for the year 2024.